<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>redis on 仲夏园</title><link>https://goplscn.github.io/tags/redis/</link><description>Recent content in redis on 仲夏园</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 13:33:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://goplscn.github.io/tags/redis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Redis 简介</title><link>https://goplscn.github.io/en/post/introduction-to-redis/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 13:33:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://goplscn.github.io/en/post/introduction-to-redis/</guid><description>Introduction to Redis Redis is an open source (BSD licensed), in-memory data structure store, used as a database, cache and message broker. It supports data structures such as strings, hashes, lists, sets, sorted sets with range queries, bitmaps, hyperloglogs, geospatial indexes with radius queries and streams. Redis has built-in replication, Lua scripting, LRU eviction, transactions and different levels of on-disk persistence, and provides high availability via Redis Sentinel and automatic partitioning with Redis Cluster.</description></item><item><title>Redis info 命令简介</title><link>https://goplscn.github.io/en/post/redis-info-command-intro/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 11:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://goplscn.github.io/en/post/redis-info-command-intro/</guid><description>Redis INFO Available since 1.0.0.
The INFO command returns information and statistics about the server in a format that is simple to parse by computers and easy to read by humans.
The optional parameter can be used to select a specific section of information:
server: General information about the Redis server clients: Client connections section memory: Memory consumption related information persistence: RDB and AOF related information stats: General statistics replication: Master/replica replication information cpu: CPU consumption statistics commandstats: Redis command statistics cluster: Redis Cluster section keyspace: Database related statistics It can also take the following values:</description></item></channel></rss>